<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><MovieCollection>
                    
    
    
    
    <movie>
                                        
        
        
        
        <name>Aquaman</name>
                                        
        
        
        
        <type>Action</type>
                                        
        
        
        
        <performers>Jason Momoa, Amber Heard, Willem Dafoe</performers>
                                        
        
        
        
        <release_year>2018</release_year>
                                        
        
        
        
        <rating>7.6</rating>
                                        
        
        
        
        <review>I really love this film. Everyone talks about the GCI in Aquaman,but what moves me most is its style ,so called "old fashioned fun" .Here I'll talk about this.

First of all, the story of Aquaman is classic enough (that is, the old-fashioned set of some people), which is the journey of superhero treasure hunt. In an interview with James wan in"WorldScreen"magazine, James said that this is a very classic narrative technique. The growth of Arthur is like the growth of heroes in Spielberg, Cameron and Lucas movies. When Wan was a child, he watched the works of these masters grow up and always wanted to make such a movie, so this retro style is intentional. The facts also prove that the classic story will not be outdated. However, we can also understand from another angle that Wan did not try to try the dark and deep story style, but from the direction of being good at commercial blockbusters. In short, even if you don't have interest in the retro story, the level of the plot is definitely qualified in the super-Hero movie.

Second, it is the retro feel of the picture. On the one hand, many dazzling special effects brought us back to Avatar and the Lord of the Rings until the shock of the first Star Wars, and the imaginative and fascinating atmosphere of the underwater world is obviously a tribute to the classic fantasy sci-fi movies, like those of Star Wars. Just like classic fantasy operatic movie opens the window of imagination for us. On the other hand, James indicates that the film is expected to be like special effects movies in japan(like Ultraman and Godzilla in last century ). No wonder the friend who watched the movie with me shouted "The clothes looks cheap" when he first saw the soldiers of Atlantis. ..... I believe that it is not a problem to add more cool special effects to the soldiers, but James chose a very traditional approach , allowing the actors to fight in plastic armor and add to the film. A little bit of childlike beauty! Seeing this armor design is a little touched. We seem to be able to see james that realize the childhood special movie dreams,hiding behind the viewfinder and snickering.

And......To be honest,I'm little worried about Aquaman2,which is said to have been planned by Warner bros because the first episode is too successful,but I don't believe James will direct it again(just like SAW and Fast&amp;Furious,he did once and did the BEST)And I'm also worried about Birds of Prey because the director is too young ...looking DCU(or DCEU) movies is funny ,we must stand some boring films ,but sometimes DC gives us BIG surprise.</review>
                                    
    
    
    
    </movie>
                
    
    
    
    <movie>
                                
        
        
        <name>Zootopia</name>
                                
        
        
        <type>Cartoon</type>
                                
        
        
        <performers>Ginnifer Goodwin, Jason Bateman</performers>
                                
        
        
        <release_year>2016</release_year>
                                
        
        
        <rating>9.2</rating>
                                
        
        
        <review>From the largest elephant to the smallest shrew, the city of Zootopia is a mammal metropolis where various animals live and thrive. When Judy Hopps becomes the first rabbit to join the police force, she quickly learns how tough it is to enforce the law. Determined to prove herself, Judy jumps at the opportunity to solve a mysterious case. Unfortunately, that means working with Nick Wilde, a wily fox who makes her job even harder.</review>
                            
    
    
    </movie>
            
    
    
    <movie>
                        
        
        <name>Titanic</name>
                        
        
        <type>Romance</type>
                        
        
        <performers>Leonardo DiCaprio, Kate Winslet</performers>
                        
        
        <release_year>1997</release_year>
                        
        
        <rating>9.3</rating>
                        
        
        <review>This has been my favorite movie since I was a young child. It is very emotional and is for mature children. This is a great movie for mature tweens and teens, a MUST SEE!!!</review>
                    
    
    </movie>
        
    
    <movie>
                
        <name>Beauty and the Beast</name>
                
        <type>Romance</type>
                
        <performers>Emma Watson, Luke Evans</performers>
                
        <release_year>2017</release_year>
                
        <rating>7.2</rating>
                
        <review>The movie was extraordinary. I believe the real Roger Ebert would've given it 4 stars. I found the major turning point of the movie, Belle's development of affection for the Beast, worked better here than in the cartoon. The acting of the two leads and their complex human facial expressions gave key moments like this emotional weight and believability that cartoons just can't capture. The set design, art direction and action scenes are as good as it gets in modern blockbuster movies. And they are properly the interludes to the real story, not the focus of the movie. The castle, with its towering parapets, dark chasms, endless hallways and winding staircases is one of the most striking locations ever captured on film. But the special effects never threaten to become the focus of the movie because the original story is so strong and so faithfully adhered to here. The leads sell their romantic relationship completely and the supporting cast is as brilliant and perfectly pitched as they come. Every one of the movie's remade scenes does justice to the original cartoon. While the scattered original material is more hit or miss, the bulk of this film is a powerfully effective retelling of a great Disney story. As for the "gay" "controversy," if Smithers on The Simpsons wasn't a problem for you, then nothing in this movie will be.</review>
            
    </movie>
    
    <movie>
        <name>Love, Simon</name>
        <type>Romance</type>
        <performers>Nick Robinson, Jennifer Garner, Josh Duhamel</performers>
        <release_year>2018</release_year>
        <rating>8.3</rating>
        <review>I didn't think I would, but - I loved it.

The first 15 minutes or so, I cringed a few times, thinking it was going to be too clever, too cute, and too precious for its own good.

But even my cynical, hard-hearted self soon melted with the realization that the intelligence, depth, and charm were all legitimate and sincere.

I left the theater with a full heart and am confident "Love, Simon" will remain with me as one of my favorites of this new film year.</review>
    </movie>
</MovieCollection>
